<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lancerharris Learns</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lancerharris Learns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on DataCamp’s course: Multiple and Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>/2019/01/19/notes-on-datacamp-s-course-multiple-and-logistic-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/19/notes-on-datacamp-s-course-multiple-and-logistic-regression/</guid>
      <description>I’ve finished DataCamp’s course Multiple and Logistic Regression and have left with a much better understanding of both topics. Of particular interest to me was learning what it means to add more than one explanatory variable to a model, what interaction terms do to a model, and how to interpret the scales of a logistic regression model. In other statistics courses I have taken I did not learn that adding another categorical explanatory variable to a model leads to what is called the “parallel slopes model”, nor did I know that adding a categorical interaction term had a geometric interpretation of two lines with differing slopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working through DataCamp’s: Introduction to Machine Learning with R</title>
      <link>/2019/01/09/working-through-datacamp-s-introduction-to-machine-learning-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/09/working-through-datacamp-s-introduction-to-machine-learning-with-r/</guid>
      <description>I’ve finished the Introduction to machine learning with R course and wanted to write about the course and share my notes on the first couple of chapters.
Thoughts on the course as a whole This course was longer than your typical DataCamp course but was well worth the extra time. I think I’ve been half consciously half subconsciously afraid to start machine learning for a while, thinking that I wasn’t ready for the abstract nature of the subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a new learning journey</title>
      <link>/2019/01/01/starting-a-new-learning-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/01/starting-a-new-learning-journey/</guid>
      <description>With the new year comes new resolutions, and creating this post on this website is one of them! I’ve created this website, with the help of the glorious blogdown package, to achieve some analysis goals. There is really only one goal and that is to LEARN TO DO ANALYSIS! But I’ve broken down that goal into smaller parts for the sake of over planning:
My #RStats goals for 2019:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>